<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<!-- Orcs | Thrall -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_THRALL" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thrall, son of Durotan and Draka, is the former Warchief of the restored shamanistic Horde, founder of the nation of Durotar in Kalimdor and one of the second wave of shaman.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- END Orcs | Thrall -->
		<!-- Tauren | CAIRNE_BLOODHOOF -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_CAIRNE_BLOODHOOF" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cairne Bloodhoof was the High Chieftain of the united tribes of the tauren, chieftain of the Bloodhoof, leader of Thunder Bluff, and the final wielder of the Bloodhoof Runespear. Allying with the Horde upon its arrival on the shores of Kalimdor, Cairne stood as one of its wisest and most venerated leaders, until his unfortunate death in a duel against Garrosh Hellscream, the new Warchief of the Horde. He was succeeded as chief by his son Baine Bloodhoof.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- END Tauren | CAIRNE_BLOODHOOF -->
		<!-- Stormwind | ANDUIN_WRYNN -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_ANDUIN_WRYNN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Anduin Llane Wrynn is the King of Stormwind, High King of the Alliance, and commander of all Alliance forces  since the death of his father, Varian Wrynn. In contrast to his decisive warrior father, Anduin is contemplative and diplomatic, as well as a priest of the Church of the Holy Light.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- END Stormwind | ANDUIN_WRYNN -->
		<!-- Dwarf | FALSTAD_WILDHAMMER -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_FALSTAD_WILDHAMMER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Falstad Wildhammer, is the High Thane of the Wildhammer clan. He ruled the Wildhammer clan from Aerie Peak in the Hinterlands following the departure of Kurdran Wildhammer and joined his companions Rhonin and Vereesa in freeing the Dragon Queen Alexstrasza from Grim Batol. Since the Cataclysm, he serves as a member of the Council of Three Hammers in Ironforge. Falstad attempts to bring balance within the Council and maintains strong diplomatic ties abroad.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- END Dwarf | FALSTAD_WILDHAMMER -->
		<!-- Orcs | VAROK_SAURFANG -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_VAROK_SAURFANG" Language="en_US">
			<Text>High Overlord Varok Saurfang is a renowned orc warrior of the Blackrock clan and a famed veteran of the First, Second, and Third Wars. He served as Orgrim Doomhammer's second-in-command during the Second War, and as Supreme Commander of the combined Might of Kalimdor, rallying the army against the qiraji of Ahn'Qiraj in Silithus. He later led the Kor'kron against the Scourge in Northrend, and assisted Thrall during the Siege of Orgrimmar. Saurfang took up the position as leader of the Orgrimmar orcs and now resides in Grommash Hold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- END Orcs | VAROK_SAURFANG -->
		<!-- BURNING_LEGION | KILJAEDEN -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_KILJAEDEN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kil'jaeden was a powerful eredar demon lord and the second in rank of the Burning Legion 25,000 years ago, Kil'jaeden, Archimonde and Velen were the leaders of the benevolent eredar people of Argus. When the Dark Titan Sargeras arrived and offered them the answer to the most important question there was, "what is the one true underlying flaw of the universe?", the eredar, as a knowledge-seeking race, accepted, led by Kil'jaeden and Archimonde. Sargeras blessed them with unimaginable power, turning the eredar into demons who would help Sargeras get rid of that flaw, while Velen and his followers fled, renaming themselves the draenei.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_THE_BLACKCITY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Black City</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_FELBAZE_INGRESS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Felbaze Ingress</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_FELSOUL_HOLD" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Felsoul Hold</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_BURNING_FARONAAR" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Burning Faronaar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_JAEDENAR" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jaedenar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_BURNING_CONSTELLAS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Burning Constellas</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_MANNOROC_COVEN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mannoroc Coven</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_SHOKTHOKAR" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Shok'thokar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_TOMB_SARGERAS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tomb of Sargeras</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- END BURNING_LEGION | KILJAEDEN -->
		<!-- BURNING_LEGION | SARGERAS -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_SARGERAS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sargeras is the creator and leader of the Burning Legion. Sargeras was once the Champion of the Pantheon, chosen to defend the worlds the titans had ordered. However, while he once served as a guardian and protector, he is now working to destroy all world-souls and life in the universe, and undo what the titans had strived for ages to achieve.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- END BURNING_LEGION | SARGERAS -->
		<!-- BURNING_LEGION | VARIMATHRAS -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_VARIMATHRAS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Varimathras is a dreadlord in the service of the Burning Legion. He was forced into allying with the Forsaken, under the direct control of Sylvanas Windrunner, in exchange for sparing his life after he and his brothers were overcome by her undead forces. Though he swore allegiance to Sylvanas, Varimathras remained loyal to the Legion and eventually staged a coup for control of the Undercity.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- END BURNING_LEGION | VARIMATHRAS -->
		<!-- TWILIGHT_HAMMER | Cho'Gall -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_CHOGALL" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cho'gall was a powerful ogre mage, Initiate of the Fifth Circle of the Shadow Council, and Chieftain of the Twilight's Hammer clan. Fleeing to Kalimdor and taking refuge within the ruined city of Ahn'Qiraj, Cho'gall's body became warped by the power of the Old God C'Thun. Cho'gall aligned himself and the Twilight's Hammer with the corrupted Aspect and his allies, the powerful Elemental Lords Al'Akir and Ragnaros, to help usher in the end times. Overseeing the cult's efforts from his citadel in the Twilight Highlands.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_BASTION_TWILIGHT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Bastion of Twilight</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_BLACK_ROCK_MT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Black Rock Mountain</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_SEAT_CHOSEN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Seat of the Chosen</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_TWILIGHT_GAUNTLET" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Twilight Gauntlet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_DOOM_VIGIL" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Doom’s Vigil</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_FORGE_OF_SUPPLICATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Forge of Supplication</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_SULFURON_SPIRE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sulfuron Spire</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- END TWILIGHT_HAMMER | Cho'Gall -->
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
